What was it?
Ever since last night,
I've had this feeling
I'm supposed to do something…
Boy, my shoes and bag
sure feel heavy today.
Huh?
Th-This house…
Why?
Somehow I ended up
walking to Rohan-Sensei's house.
The door's open…
I'd like to drop in and
thank him for yesterday,
but I'll be late for school.
I probably shouldn't.
Being a manga artist,
he's probably still asleep.
I really shouldn't just barge in.
This really isn't
such a good idea…
Rohan-sensei..
He's working with
such a chilling expression.
What is this…
I can't shake the feeling that
being here is actually terrifying.
What is it?
So you made it.
I've been waiting.
You're right on time.
Huh?
Forgive me, but could I
ask you to wait for a moment?
Just two more pages,
and next week's manuscript
will be complete.
It'll only take about
twenty minutes.
Twenty minutes?
Did he just say
two pages in twenty minutes?
I must've misheard him.
Two pages in twenty minutes
from scratch?
That'd be impossible…
And next week's?
He just showed us yesterday
this week's manuscript,
and he'd just finished it.
What?! Straight to pen?!
I-I don't believe it…
Such complex composition,
and without any sketching!
He's hammering it out
with no hesitation…
And with the backgrounds!
W-What was that?!
I didn't get a good look.
What'd he just do?!
What?! "Beta" coloring?!
He's flicking the ink around
like shurikens,
with perfect precision
and not a single stray mark!
Th-That technique…
Isn't beta coloring done
with a brush?!
BOOM
The beta coloring's already done!
It took him only
about two minutes, start to finish!
All thanks to you, Koichi.
My creative urges runneth over!
My appetite to draw is insatiable!
I want to draw more!
Drawing nineteen pages in one night
is something I've
never ever experienced before!
At this very moment,
a masterpiece is being born!
Your life experiences
are astonishing!
- Huh?
- I'm basing my story
- What…?
- on your experience, Koichi!
Get cracking!
I want your next reality!
Show me your next page!
Your weight decreases with
every page I take,
but you don't mind, right?
For you will become a masterpiece,
immortalized for all eternity!
FLIP
Now I remember!
Heaven's Door!
Y-You're a Stand user!
JOJO'S BIZARRE ADVENTURE
DIAMOND IS UNBREAKABLE
A demon's crept into
our everyday life
It's about to take away
something precious
Our peace has already
crumbled long ago
So casually, so nonchalantly
It's taken from us
before we know it
If we want it back,
now's the chance
With the sharpness of
the piercing arrow
The beauty of two souls united
Wherever you go, chase you
Whenever, chase you
I will chase you
Nowhere to escape
Start running, I will chase you
Tomorrow, chase you
My fists will be the one
to show you
Tenacity decides
who will win or lose
So I chase you
Look…
EPISODE 15
LET'S GO TO
THE MANGA ARTIST'S HOUSE, PART 2
It's not even done yet,
and this single panel
could be a book in and of itself!
This is amazing!
I'm maturing…
as a manga artist and a Stand user!
Now if you don't mind,
Koichi, I'm going to read this.
Interesting…
If I'm not mistaken,
those are the faces of
Shining Diamond's Josuke Higashikata
and The Hand's Okuyasu Nijimura.
But good heavens…
Why are they coming to my house?
There's no way Koichi
would've mentioned me to those two.
How peculiar…
Huh?
I-It's Josuke and Okuyasu!
I have no idea how
they found me here, but…
I've got to get them to save me!
Somehow!
Somehow…
I have to get them to save me!
Huh? Okuyasu and Josuke?
How did you know I was here?
Now, then…
For now, Josuke and
Okuyasu are of no interest to me.
I'll finish up the last
two pages for next week,
and seize even more material
from Koichi!
I can hardly contain myself!
Huh? You were watching
a manga artist at work?
This is where he works?
Rohan Kishibe?
Is he famous or something?
Ever heard of him, Josuke?
Nah. Remember,
even that bastard Hazamada
gave me a hard time for not
knowing what Perman was.
That wasn't it.
That wasn't what I wanted
to say to them.
But what was it?
Well, you were staggering around
so we thought we better tail you,
but if everything's
hunky dory, then all right.
Nothing to worry about.
Thanks.
Aren't you gonna come in
and observe with me?
Nah, I'll pass.
Famous people make me nervous.
Same here.
Knowing you weren't with some chick
is enough for me.
See ya, Koichi.
Bye.
I'm drawing a blank.
I know I meant to tell
them something really important.
I remember now!
I-I was going to ask for help!
Josuke! Okuyasu!
See you guys at school in a bit!
Yeah!
Don't be late.
Got it!
N-No!
That's not what I wanted to say!
I CANNOT ATTACK
THE MANGA ARTIST, ROHAN KISHIBE
CANNOT
Damn! I'm not
able to ask them for help.
This Stand is beyond terrifying!
Heaven's Door is unshakable!
It's invincible!
Ah, I see…
At this rate, he's going to rip
everything out of me and kill me!
Someone's entered the mansion!
What did you do downstairs, Koichi?
Huh?
Okuyasu!
Hold it right there!
Just keep looking straight ahead.
Don't try anything,
or I'll crush you with my Stand,
you doodling s.o.b.
Okuyasu!
I don't know how you knew
I was in danger, but I'm ecstatic!
It appears you've had an epiphany.
I hadn't noticed before,
but that little wound on your hand
must've given away
your little predicament.
I suppose you scratched it
or caught it on something
while you were crawling.
I-I was so entranced,
I didn't notice…
That's what gave it away,
right, Okuyasu Nijimura?
Stand name: The Hand…
You have a complex about
your dead brother, Keicho,
and whenever you try to
make a decision,
you wish that
your brother were there.
Wha…
What? Who the hell are you?
Hey, Koichi, tell me what
this guy's Stand is!
W-Well…
I-I can't!
I can't say anything that would put
Rohan Kishibe at a disadvantage.
One look at a single panel,
and it's all over!
I desperately want to tell you…
don't look!
Don't look at that manga!
Hey, I said don't move!
Okuyasu, you were of
no concern to me,
but all of that changed
when you set foot in this house.
I'll have to turn you
into an inspiration, too.
You bastard!
What?!
H-He's fast!
Okuyasu!
What the hell is this?!
Josuke Higashikata,
I know you're hiding over there.
HEAVEN'S DOOR
Okuyasu!
What the hell is up
with this manga freak?
Oh, be quiet.
Now, then… Koichi,
I have a question.
Huh?
Why do you think Josuke Higashikata
is hiding behind that door?
Well? What do you think?
Why won't he show himself, Koichi?
Josuke is hiding so
he won't catch sight of your manga.
Indeed, right on the money.
How very astute of you.
Okuyasu Nijimura knew
nothing about my Heaven's Door,
so he fell right into my trap.
Conversely, his ignorance
exposed to Josuke Higashikata
the workings of my Stand.
At this point, I can't help
but feel I'm at somewhat,
no, I'm at a significant
disadvantage.
But Josuke Higashikata has
another reason for his concealment.
What do you think that is?
So that this no longer continues,
I will have to resort to something
in order to smoke him out
of his hiding place.
He's busy figuring out
how to massacre you!
That's also correct.
But that's not the exact answer
I was looking for.
The answer I want is…
Josuke Higashikata
is contemplating whether
he should flee this mansion
all by his lonesome.
Josuke would never do that!
Right, Koichi.
Your files tell me that it is in
Josuke Higashikata's character
to never abandon you two.
But, the manga artist tends to,
on account of his work,
consider every conceivable possibility
at every conceivable moment.
In this situation,
with this protagonist,
what would he or she do?
In this case, Josuke fleeing
with knowledge of my Stand
would put me in quite the catch-22.
Run… That's not a bad idea.
He could go get Jotaro,
and if Yukako found out
what's happened to you,
she'd be enraged.
Ah! She'd beat him with her hair!
Though I really don't
want to see her again!
Come on, Josuke!
Hurry up and let them know!
You fools!
I explained that to you exactly
so it wouldn't happen!
Okuyasu! I already wrote that
into your body!
Huh?
I give you permission to explain
the content of my missive, Koichi.
No!
What'd he write, Koichi?
B-But that's… No…
We're completely trapped!
There's no running from this!
That's why I'm asking you
what he wrote, Koichi!
IF JOSUKE HIGASHIKATA CAUSES
TROUBLE FOR ROHAN KISHIBE,
I WILL BURN MYSELF TO DEATH
B-Burn myself to death?!
You'll kill yourself if Josuke
so much as tries to help us!
H-Hey, hey! I burn myself to death?
That's crazy talk! Like I'd ever do
something so horrible to myself!
Huh?
You will! He's invincible!
We're completely incapable
of defying him!
Stop! My right hand!
You decided to join us.
I don't think he
decided anything…
Something dragged him out here.
Ah… Rather a childish
and simple-minded move,
but potentially effective as well.
There's nowhere to run
in this cramped room.
One knockout blow to me,
and Heaven's Door
will release its grip,
and Okuyasu won't commit suicide.
Josuke!
Closing his eyes is simple-minded,
but it just might work.
As long as he doesn't
see the manuscript,
Heaven's Door is powerless.
Keep coming… straight ahead!
Which means…
All I have to do is get you
to open your eyes somehow.
Oh! He's standing firm.
Bad news…
If he keeps charging at
me like that, all bets will be off.
SECONDS
If I were a manga protagonist,
what would I do?
How would I get him
to open his eyes?
Go, Josuke!
Hurry up, Josuke!
That's it!
Something in Koichi's file…
There! This is it!
Comments like,
"Your hair makes me laugh, Josuke!"
Or, "Wasn't that on trend, like,
twenty or thirty years ago?"
And, "You think you look cool?"
Like that, right?
I guess that's what sets him off.
Inconceivable, yes,
but the files do not lie.
It's 100% true.
What did you just say?
J-Josuke, settle down!
Why don't you try
and say that again!
There they are…
Didn't you hear me?
You may think that hair looks cool,
but on you it looks like shit.
Lame!
Though that noggin of yours may make
a disgusting pigeon very happy.
That's a strong "may," though.
Heaven's Door!
I win.
Huh?!
What?!
W-What the hell?
I-I know I opened his eyes
and showed him the manuscript!
W-We're back to normal!
But I showed it to him… Why?
Now where the hell'd
you stuff off to?!
Get back out here, goddammit!
He's not really seeing…
He's not really seeing?
You mean he's so worked up,
he doesn't even know
what he's doing?
Where are you,
you manga-obsessed asshole?!
Get out here!
Yeah… Any kind of hair insult,
it doesn't matter if it's from
a comic or someone's mouth,
he flies into a blind rage.
I had no idea he had such a temper.
It's beyond my wildest imagination.
What?
There was a facet of
Josuke's personality
that even Koichi didn't know?
That means it wasn't
written in the file!
Why? Why does he get
so mad over his hair?
There has to be a reason… Why?
I show no mercy!
I won't take that bullshit
from anyone!
The reason…
I think I may've heard it before.
That just might be why…
Huh? What are you talking about?
It was when Josuke
was a kid, but…
I'll try and remember
the story as best I can,
I might have to fill in some gaps.
Josuke was four,
and he had passed out from
an inexplicably high fever.
For fifty days, he was within
a hair's breadth of death.
Josuke…
He found out later that it was
right around the time
Jotaro and Mr. Joestar
traveled to Egypt to
defeat the man named DIO.
With no idea what was happening,
Josuke's mom headed to
a hospital in S City.
But Morioh was in the middle
of its worst blizzard in 18 years.
It's no use… What should I do?
Nobody ever drives around here,
and there's not
a payphone in sight.
I should've called
an ambulance from the house.
I shouldn't have brought
Josuke out in this snow.
That's when it happened.
W-What do you want? Go away!
YOUR KID IS SICK, RIGHT?
I'll PUSH YOUR CAR.
Huh?
NOW STEP ON THE GAS.
ONCE YOU GAIN TRACTION,
DON'T STOP. JUST GUN IT…
OR YOU'LL GET STUCK AGAIN.
Got it…
Thank you!
His mom eventually
tried to search for the young man,
but found no information.
That young man may've not
personally saved his life,
but in the eyes of
four-year-old Josuke,
he was his hero.
He became a permanent inspiration,
his role model for life.
An affront to that part of him,
triggers something
deep in his heart.
I don't know who he is
or where he's from,
but as a tribute to him,
I adopted the same hairstyle.
I won't put up with
anyone who disrespects it,
I don't care who it is.
It's disrespectful to him.
That has to be the reason.
I thought Josuke
was just making it up,
so I wasn't listening
very carefully.
Huh… I had no idea.
Rohan's holding a pen!
Bastard! At it again, huh?!
N-No…
I-I wanted to jot this all down
before I lost consciousness.
What a magnificent story!
And I just had
an amazing experience.
I'm elated.
Experiences like that are rare.
If I can just incorporate it
into my own work…
I'm so blessed.
I'm so glad I moved to Morioh.
It's no use.
As long as he's alive, he won't stop
searching for manga material,
no matter how
horrible the experience.
At this point,
you have to commend him.
Good and bad aside,
I have to admire his outlook.
He's truly a super manga artist.
There you are, manga artist!
I'm not done punching you!
I think ya have to
commend him, too.
Y-Yeah…
ROHAN KISHIBE'S
PINK DARK BOY
— SUSPENSION NOTICE —
SORRY!
THANK YOU FOR YOUR CONTINUED
READERSHIP OF PINK DARK BOY.
DUE TO PERSONAL MATTERS,
OUR PUBLICATION WILL BE
SUSPENDED FOR ONE MONTH.
(FROM THE EDITORS)
Rohan Kishibe's Pink Dark Boy
will be suspended
for one month.
EPISODE 16
LET'S GO HUNTING!